Or a style of water.
How do we get the vote from the government?
Let's prime.
The only product that we've cried from a forsake on community,
spiritually, socially, and economically,
may we work together to create a place
where all we're valued,
where justice and righteousness prevailed.
and where the needs of a most vulnerable are met.
We pray for those who are in positions of leadership
within our community, grant a wisdom,
the ceremony and humility as they serve the needs of the people.
May they be guided by your truth and by your love.
On your Lord, we thank you for the gift of community
and for the bonds of love and fellowship they deny us.
Help us to be instruments of your peace,
shining your light and spreading your love prayer
where we go on here.
I'd like to leave you to light by the word you'll feel good.
Congratulations to the flag of the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands, one nation,
another god, indivisible with the beauty of justice,
or all.
I'm scared of personal chances, and you have a body
that might have less to be able to take the action
than you think you've heard.
On the claims list for an issue that you'll see
that under the GRDA for the purchase power,
that there is a light payment fee of 16,000 dollars,
and that we work one day like we're paying that.
And so that's the thing I am working with them to get it right.
And we have since done, we're going to be paying at a stage stage,
but I didn't check it for a wire in a stage,
which I don't know if it's going to go to it.
So we don't know much about that.
Sorry, I just wanted to identify that much now
that we are working on getting it right at it,
and also that we have worked on things to get it next to where it doesn't occur.
So just to my fear, obviously, how are they working with you on your daily life?
I reached out and I loved your voice bells.
I loved my bright cellphones, so that I didn't have to worry about it.
I was at my desk, and I had them to pursue their lives.
I would like to have a question.
Question.
Number.
Six.
That's for the number 16th.
Twenty-one more ready to meeting.
And set the number 23, 2024 special meeting.
Number.
Be careful.
So, this is a reclaimed award, this is for a property evaluation, this part of the
Civil Aviation.
Actually, it's not about the Civil Aviation.
So, the 300,000 are committed to the civil Aviation.
We currently have a thousand, something like 9,000, something like change in this plan,
and it's a thousand, one hundred.
There's a group that we have about, 72,000, 71 dollar, and something like this.
Post-troubles.
Doctor.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Paul.
Congratulations.
The boat evolved, because of the power storage, power purchase, and agreement letter with Jim 7 solar LLC.
So, this kind of e-centice, a hydrozone, they were wanting to gather a solar system for the city, and to them when they're also out here.
The looks in treating to the staff, but the problem with doing this is if we were to enter into such a way that we'd be in violation of contract with GRN.
That's the problem.
I mean, the contract with GRN goes until 2022, and there it is.
I mean, the system can't even have the money.
I mean, there's one to the other, and it's possible.
So, that's our problem with there.
We're stuck.
So we do, we do, we do, we divide, start a percent of this from them.
Yeah.
No, because the contract, the contract, the contract, allows 20 percent.
But we have to own and operate the system.
It's just right.
That's right.
So either way, we still have this problem,
we're in the larger area of the contract.
And chances are, you're probably not the less.
If you dug in with this, it will be more on your contract.
Is there any loopholes?
Well, there is a possibility that we can cancel it.
10 years or so.
So that take place.
20, 2,000, 32.
Have any of their floors?
Have any other cities that are in similar position?
We have that run into many cities that are in quite the unique position that you are in.
It's least in terms of the longevity of that contract.
I mean, if you do anything with any flexibility.
That's what we were proposing is, is this non-binding letter for now.
So we can actually explore the options for you.
And I can just find things, legal and others to sort of try to find options.
Non-binding.
Well, it says it's non-binding.
Right, it's just being not binding.
But it's kind of binding but necessarily not binding.
But what's intended for the new binding is just a process of being with talk,
confidentialism.
And it's a binding part of the round of the round, not binding.
Part of the round compositionality in us engaging in the process, not around specific PPA or
remit that we would be working on during this part of this.
So that's the binding part, he's just in, for its confidential.
If you'd be reading.
Can you just conversation with me?
Make a little bit of a move to get that.
Can you make a marker?
Right.
Don't go.
You said?
Don't hide the parts.
It was an eye.
The discussion of technical.
Tintial economic development to the sale of real property or enhancement of real property
to be provided by the city and or on its trust authorities as part of the economic.
the fulfillment of the project.
So as you can see from the next item
that is over wanting to talk about here,
is selling officially authorized in the sale
all or part of lots number six through 19
to the Ottawa Tribe.
The reason why we are, excuse me,
six through 19 of a plot 55 of the original plan.
The reason why it's worth that way
is there are a couple of things
that we need to work out with them.
One is that there is still the need
to have a plot type of lawsuit that we've discussed
over the last several weeks.
And that would be a can be out to the same.
The second is, at this point, the time,
plot number 10 is dedicated to the public
as a walkway.
We can change that, but we don't know from then
which one they push, not their wanting.
But we're thinking if it be part of it,
that's our thinking, we don't know what they're thinking.
That parcel would be excluded from the sale.
You would still own that parcel and use that parcel.
Whichever one it is, they're wanting.
We would still use that parcel as they let it walk.
We had to do that.
That's the one right.
We had this discussion, but I never found
the dark part being the walkway.
That's what we thought.
OK.
And then the third is that, on my mind,
a lot, 19 at the south end, there's a matter of 13 or so
inches that I need to say for purposes of the Foundation
of the Charles Maxwell's.
I don't think we talked about that.
Did we go?
Annembers.
We're going to make sure.
I'm going to make sure.
But we probably need to get some of them.
So anyway, the point is that if you approve the motion,
then we can proceed and get these things to our five eventually.
Do you think we'll make sure you make a motion to the group itself?
Yeah.
I think we'll have all of our part on a lot,
including the walkway being administered to the art part.
Thank you.
Marker?
Mark?
So, we have another new business committee, which the residents have posted on this agenda.
12 staff reports, 15, trust between the announcements.
So, 14,000, 15,000.
14,000, 15,000.